

MURAI-SZABADI CINTIA

FRONT-FND DEVELOPER



+3630/646-1228



xzabadicintia@gmail.com



https://ms-cinti.github.io/pet-project/



Budapest - Érd



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ cintia-murai-szabadi-724a4023b/



https://github.com/ms-cinti

EDUCATION

FRONT-END DEVELOPER Codecool 2022

ELEMENTARY SCHOOL TEACHER University of ELTE 2014-2018

HARD SKILLS

Javascript React Node.is **JSON** Rest API HTML CSS Docker GIT MongoDB Photoshop Illustrator

SOFT SKILLS

InDesign

Good communication Team player

Figma

Problem solving Fast learner

Critical thinking Good listener

Motivation to learn Creativity

Time management Adaptability

ABOUT ME

After graduating and working for three years as a teacher, I have decided to change my career and look for new challenges in IT. In addition to various online courses, I have completed Codecool's Front-End Developer program which further increased my passion and motivation in working in this field. Since 2022, I am working as a Creative Developer at McCann Erickson where I had the opportunity to develop both my hard and soft skillset necessary for different projects. Overall, I am a highly motivated and easy-going person who always looks for opportunity to learn and develop as a collegue.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SEPT 2022 - PRESENT

McCann Erickson Advertising Agency, Budapest Creative Developer

Developing HMTL/CSS/Javascript codes along customer

Supporting the review process of existing products and adjusting them based on feedbacks from customers Designing materials presented to the customers along different optimization conditions and quality standards Helping graphical design team in their projects including graphical softwares such as Photoshop, Figma, Illustrator and PowerPoint

2018 - 2021

Gárdonyi Géza Elementary School, Budapest Reményik Sándor Elementary School, Boba **Elementary School Teacher**

Developed lesson plans

Established and enforced a set of rules for the classroom Kept parents updated on their child's progress Encouraged students to learn as much as possible Monitored each student's progress and provided extra mentorship as needed

LANGUAGE

ENGLISH B2 (TIT-TELC, 2017)

HOBBIES









